verybestquotes.com 2017-05-17

# The Quote Garden Privacy Policy

**  The Quote Garden** **™**   
**  “I dig old books.”** **™**  
**  Est. 1998**  

**PRIVACY POLICY**

WBS Publishing, LLC dba The Quote Garden respects the privacy of the visitors of its Website, the home page of which is located at http://www.quotegarden.com/ (the “Website”) and we strive to provide the safest possible environment for our visitors. Please read this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) carefully, because by visiting our Website, you are bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. You agree that by accessing our Website you expressly and voluntarily consent to our use and disclosure of the information that you submit and you expressly and voluntarily consent to receive emails, as set forth below.

**Overview**

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information you submit to us through our Website and to demonstrate our commitment to protecting the information that you submit. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you have submitted through our Website and does not apply to any other information or Website. Please be advised that this Policy may be amended at any time without notice and it is your responsibility to read it carefully and review any changes that may be made.

**Your Information: Email Communications, Information Collected**

Presently, no personal information from visitors is gathered or tracked by our Website. The only personal information we see from visitors occurs when visitors send emails to The Quote Garden. No personal information is exchanged through the Website if you attempt to contact and email us. We do not share private email information (names, email addresses, email content) sent through the act of emailing with outside parties. However, please note that we have no control or responsibility over the privacy policies and security of personal email accounts and email service providers.

The Quote Garden does not provide or sell your personal identifiable information to other parties. We do not see any personal identifiable information when you visit the Website.

While we do not track our Website traffic, we do, however, reserve the right to receive information about your location from your IP address when accessing the Website for general site traffic monitoring.

**Use of Cookies**

We use “cookies” on our Website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies may enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information. Some of our third-party service providers also may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers, as discussed below). Please note, however, that we have no access to or control over these cookies.

You may refuse to accept cookies by altering the settings on your internet browser through the “Help” feature on your browser, or for additional assistance, you can click on the “Manage Cookies” section on the Interactive Advertising Bureau website: http://www.allaboutcookies.org. Please note that if you adjust your internet browser settings to refuse cookies, it may affect your functionality of this Website and you may be unable to access all parts of this Website.

If you withdraw your consent to receive an advertiser’s cookies, you will need to notify the advertiser directly and follow the advertiser’s instructions. The advertiser is responsible for the withdrawal of your consent. Select the advertisers you would like to block through following links:

http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

http://www.aboutads.info/choices

Please note that if you are a visitor to this Website from outside of the United States, some countries may require you to consent to the use of cookies on the Website. If you continue to visit and use the Website, we will infer such use as your consent to the use of cookies that may be found on the Website.

**Third-Party Service Providers**

Various third-party retailers, advertising entities, and other companies may place advertisements on this Website. These parties may use their own technology (such as cookies, web beacons, JavaScript, or other tracking technology) to collect information about you for analytics, statistical, and other informational purposes. The information received by these third-party advertising companies and their business partners is subject to the privacy policies of these third-party advertising companies and business partners. We have no control over the use of such technology and activity, nor are we responsible for such use.

We reserve the right to be given access to this information (including personal information, where you consent) by these third-party advertising companies and business partners which we may use for purposes including, without limitation, to better target advertising and content to you and to generate statistics and reports that help us develop our Website, content and services.

For more information about interest-based and behavioral-based advertising practices, please visit the following links:

http://www.networkadvertising.org

http://www.aboutads.info

**Links To Third-Party Websites**

Our Policy does not apply to third-party websites. We may link to third-party websites, including social media sites, and we do not have control over these websites or their use of your personal identifiable information. We are not responsible for the practices employed by third-party websites linked to or from the Website, nor the information or content contained therein. If you click on a link, the third-party operator or others may collect data and personal information about you when you visit the linked website. We have no control or responsibility over the collection and use of such information. Please check the terms of use and privacy of any linked websites you visit to find out what data they are collecting and the purposes for which they process your personal information and data.

**Other Disclosure of Personal Information**

We will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except: (1) as described in this Policy; (2) as required by court order or other government or law enforcement authorities in order to comply with the legal process or law; (3) to protect against the misuse or unauthorized use of our property; (4) to protect and defend our rights and property; and (5) to protect the personal safety or property of our visitors or the public.

**Security**

We use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. Due to the complexities of the internet and its frequently evolving technologies, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third-parties. We are therefore not liable for disclosure of personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized or unlawful acts by third-parties.

**Limitation of Liability**

You understand and agree that any dispute over privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and applicable terms and conditions of our Website. You agree that The Quote Garden’s liability for any breach of this Privacy Policy shall be limited to the value of the transactions or services provided to you by us (if any) to the extent such claim is not otherwise barred by our Terms and Conditions. You further agree that any dispute arising out of this Privacy Policy will be filed in Maricopa County, Arizona and will be governed by Arizona law.

**Disclaimer**

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information never will be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Although we have taken all necessary and reasonable steps to protect your privacy, we do not promise and you should not expect that your private communications and/or your personal information always will remain private and confidential. As a user of this Website, you understand and expressly agree to assume all responsibility and risk in your use of this Website, the information you submit and the documents you post.

**Comments and Questions**

If you have a comment or question about this Privacy Policy, please contact 

legalquotegardencom. Our Website may contain links to other sites not owned or controlled by us and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the privacy policies of other websites that may collect your personal information.

**Your Consent**

By using The Quote Garden, you are consenting to the terms and conditions pertaining to the collection and use of your information described in the Privacy Policy and you accept and agree to this Privacy Policy.

_______________________

Copyright © 2016 The Quote Garden 

**_Page Information:_**  
www.quotegarden.com/privacy-policy.html  
Last modified 2017 Feb 13 Mon 19:08 PST
